<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Waaberi&#39;s Hub</title>
    <link>/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Waaberi&#39;s Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;script src=&#34;https://tryhackme.com/badge/185942&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 17:32:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flatpaks for newbies</title>
      <link>/posts/flatpaks-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 17:32:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/flatpaks-linux/</guid>
      <description>Flatpaks are special apps that are sandboxed, and are from special repositories. The most popular Flatpak repository is Flathub, where anyone can put any Flatpak. Also, Flatpaks work for over 27 distros, which make it a good choice for deploying software. In this post, i&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to get Flatpak, and the basics of Flatpaks.
Installation It depends on your distribution, they have a setup page that shows you how to install it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu Installation Guide</title>
      <link>/posts/kubuntu-distro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 14:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kubuntu-distro/</guid>
      <description>In this post, i will show you some Linux basics and a little bit about Kubuntu. Kubuntu is a Linux distribution that is basically Ubuntu but with KDE Plasma as the desktop environment (like a GUI). I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank Zera since he wanted me to make a post about some debian based distro.
Installation The Kubuntu installation is pretty straight forward, you go to the Kubuntu Website and you download the latest LTS version.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Endeavour OS</title>
      <link>/posts/my-experience-with-endeavour-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 16:02:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-experience-with-endeavour-os/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, i decided to install Endeavour OS, an Arch Linux based distro, on my laptop. I was bored of Kubuntu, and it had issues with my CPU since it was not well supported by the LTS kernel. In general, i also prefer getting updates faster. All of this made me want to switch to a rolling release distro.
The first distro that i tried to install was Manjaro, it was everything i wanted, however, the installer would freeze, something that holded me back from trying it (it did work on a VM).</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
