<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Waaberi&#39;s Hub</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Waaberi&#39;s Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Made with a brain and some milk</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 14:11:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu Installation Guide</title>
      <link>/posts/kubuntu-distro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 14:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kubuntu-distro/</guid>
      <description>In this post, i will show you some Linux basics and a little bit about Kubuntu. Kubuntu is a Linux distribution that is basically Ubuntu but with KDE Plasma as the desktop environment (like a GUI). I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank Zera since he wanted me to make a post about some debian based distro.
Installation The Kubuntu installation is pretty straight forward, you go to the Kubuntu Website and you download the latest LTS version.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brave Browser, should you use it?</title>
      <link>/posts/brave-review-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 17:10:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/brave-review-2020/</guid>
      <description>Brave is a popular chromium based browser made by Brendan Eich (co-founder of Firefox) that is open source. Brave comes built-in with an ad blocker, and because of that, it&amp;rsquo;s faster than Chrome. Many people like it, but should you use it? That is the question i will try to answer.
Good stuff Brave blocks ads, and upgrades your connection to HTTPS when it can. This makes it better than typical browsers such as Chrome for privacy.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience With Endeavour OS</title>
      <link>/posts/my-experience-with-endeavour-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 16:02:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-experience-with-endeavour-os/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, i decided to install Endeavour OS, an Arch Linux based distro, on my laptop. I was bored of Kubuntu, and it had issues with my CPU since it was not well supported by the LTS kernel. In general, i also prefer getting updates faster. All of this made me want to switch to a rolling release distro.
The first distro that i tried to install was Manjaro, it was everything i wanted, however, the installer would freeze, something that holded me back from trying it (it did work on a VM).</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python vs JavaScript</title>
      <link>/posts/python-vs-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 21:16:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/python-vs-js/</guid>
      <description>Both languages are very good, but what should you use for what, and why? That&amp;rsquo;s what i will be discussing in this post. I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank ZaphireHacks for bringing this up, i already had this debate before, but i think it&amp;rsquo;s important to have it again.
I will be rating JS and Python with 3 points, which are:
 Performance Functionality and Difficulty  First, i think it&amp;rsquo;s important to define what we mean by Python and JavaScript, because for some points, the language itself can&amp;rsquo;t just define that because there are multiple implementations.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my blog!</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 19:59:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>This will be my blog, i made it in Hugo and it&amp;rsquo;s pretty good imo. There&amp;rsquo;s a few stuff i still gotta learn about Hugo but the docs are pretty straight forward.
Let&amp;rsquo;s see how code looks in it (i use monokai)
[print(f&amp;#34;Whats up! It&amp;#39;s number {i}&amp;#34;) for i in range(1, 100000000001)] From what i&amp;rsquo;m seeing, it looks pretty good!
In this blog, i&amp;rsquo;ll talk about computers, programming, linux and stuff like that.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why All the Hate for JavaScript?</title>
      <link>/posts/why-all-the-hate-for-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 19:32:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why-all-the-hate-for-js/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! I just wanted to ask you a question, why do so many people hate JS? Btw this is a test article, i&amp;rsquo;ll add stuff later.
Express server: const express = require(&amp;#34;express&amp;#34;) const app = express(); app.get(&amp;#34;/&amp;#34;, (req, res) =&amp;gt; { res.send(&amp;#34;Are you da legendary captain milk?&amp;#34;) }) app.listen(process.env.PORT || 3000, () =&amp;gt; console.log(&amp;#34;Server up!&amp;#34;)) 
Test test test test x2</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
